chinesefooddiy.com 2017-12-01

# ChineseFoodDIY.com Online Privacy Policy

**  
** ** ChineseFoodDIY.com Online Privacy Policy  
(Last updated on April 14, 2011)**

ChineseFoodDIY.com has established this Privacy Policy to explain how it protects and manages the personal information that it collects from you (the customer) online. 

| 

** 1.**

| 

** Consent for Collection, Use and Disclosure**  
  
---|---  
  
Your use of the ChineseFoodDIY.com site and/or your registration for ChineseFoodDIY.com products and services constitute your consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy.  If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the ChineseFoodDIY.com site. 

ChineseFoodDIY.com may occasionally update this Privacy Policy.  When it does, ChineseFoodDIY.com will also revise the “last update” date at the top of this Privacy Policy.  In addition, ChineseFoodDIY.com will seek a customer’s prior consent, by email, for any new uses or proposed disclosures of information collected from the customer prior to the change. **  **ChineseFoodDIY.com will notify customers by email **** of changes to this policy that will affect information collected from them in the future.  In certain circumstances, however, ChineseFoodDIY.com will not inform and obtain the consent of the customer, such as in connection with an investigation of a breach of an agreement, contravention of laws, an emergency where the life, health or security of an individual is threatened, the collection of a debt or in compliance with the request of a law enforcement agency or a court order.

A customer may withdraw his or her consent for collection, use and disclosure at any time by sending an email to  .  Please note that, if you do, ChineseFoodDIY.com may suspend its provision of products and services to you.  When you unsubscribe, if you fall within the guarantee period for any ChineseFoodDIY.com product and you request a refund, the guarantee will be honored. 

ChineseFoodDIY.com collects, at the time of your registration and your sign-on to its web site, certain “personal information” (information that personally identifies you) including but not limited to your name, email address, home or work address, telephone number, and information about your computer hardware and software ( _e.g._ , IP address, operating system, browser type, domain name, URL, access times, and referring web site addresses). 

ChineseFoodDIY.com has implemented this Privacy Policy to protect personal information received from its customers, and to respond to any inquiries.  The Privacy Policy also provides that ChineseFoodDIY.com will use appropriate contractual means to establish a comparable level of protection for personal information which is sent for processing by third parties on ChineseFoodDIY.com’s behalf. 

** 3.**

| 

** Purposes for Collecting Personal Information**  
  
---|---  
  
ChineseFoodDIY.com collects and uses personal information for the following Identified Purposes:

(a) 

| 

to understand customer needs regarding ChineseFoodDIY.com’s services;  
  
---|---  
  
(b)

| 

to develop and provide our web site and our products and services for our customers;  
  
---|---  
  
(c)   to fulfill your requests for products, services or information; 

(d)

| 

to communicate with customers and site visitors, when necessary, and to inform customers of upgrades, as well as of other products and services available from ChineseFoodDIY.com, its affiliates and third parties;  
  
---|---  
  
(e)

| 

to allow customers to access limited-entry areas of ChineseFoodDIY.com’s site;  
  
---|---  
  
(f)

| 

to personalize some of our services and products for you and to deliver targeted advertisements and offers from ChineseFoodDIY.com and third parties;  
  
---|---  
  
(g)

| 

to bill accounts and maintain payment records;   
  
---|---  
  
(h)

| 

to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or government request;  
  
---|---  
  
(i)

| 

to respond to a legitimate claim, or to address our reasonable belief, that you are violating the rights of any third party or any of the agreements or policies that govern your use of the ChineseFoodDIY.com site or any ChineseFoodDIY.com product or service;  
  
---|---  
  
(j)

| 

to protect the services, products or rights of ChineseFoodDIY.com, including but not limited to the security or integrity of the ChineseFoodDIY.com site; and  
  
---|---  
  
(k)

| 

to identify and resolve technical problems concerning ChineseFoodDIY.com’s site, products and services.  
  
---|---  
  
ChineseFoodDIY.com also uses personal information in an aggregate form ( _i.e._ , not individually attributable to you) for its business analysis, operational, marketing and other promotional purposes.

If we hire other companies to provide some products or services on our behalf, then we will only provide those companies the personal information they need for the Identified Purposes, and we will limit their rights to use and further disclose your personal information as appropriate in the course of their work for us.

** 4.**

| 

** Limiting the Collection of Personal Information**  
  
---|---  
  
ChineseFoodDIY.com limits its collection of personal information to only that information which is necessary for the Identified Purposes.  ChineseFoodDIY.com does not direct its site to, nor does it knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen.

When you visit the ChineseFoodDIY.com web site, a cookie may be placed on your computer or the cookie may be read if you have visited the ChineseFoodDIY.com site previously.  ChineseFoodDIY.com uses cookies to allow ChineseFoodDIY.com to determine which products and services you have already purchased so that ChineseFoodDIY.com does not provide redundant information to you, and, if you are an ChineseFoodDIY.com affiliate, to track ChineseFoodDIY.com sales made to customers referred by you so that you can receive compensation under our affiliate program.  If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the ChineseFoodDIY.com web site, you may not be able to view all the text on the screens, or to experience a personalised visit, or to subscribe to certain service and product offerings on the ChineseFoodDIY.com site.

** 5.**

| 

** Disclosure, Processing and Retention  **  
  
---|---  
  
ChineseFoodDIY.com does not sell, rent or disclose your personal information to anyone else, except:

(a)

| 

to someone you have designated to act as your agent, for one or more of the Identified Purposes (listed in Section 2, above);  
  
---|---  
  
(b)

| 

to ChineseFoodDIY.com’s employees, independent contractors, subsidiaries, affiliates, consultants, business associates, service providers, suppliers and agents, acting on  ChineseFoodDIY.com’s behalf for any of the Identified Purposes;  
  
---|---  
  
(c) 

| 

as necessary if ChineseFoodDIY.com has reason to believe that disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with ChineseFoodDIY.com’s rights or property, other users of ChineseFoodDIY.com’s web site, products or services, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities; and  
  
---|---  
  
(d)

| 

to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law.   
  
---|---  
  
In addition, as we continue to develop our business, we or our affiliates may sell or buy other businesses or entities, or we may merge with another company.  In such transactions, personal information may be one of the transferred business assets.  Also, in the event that ChineseFoodDIY.com or substantially all of its assets are acquired, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets.

Your information may be stored and processed in the United States, or in any other country in which ChineseFoodDIY.com or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities.  By using this web site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. 

After your account becomes inactive (that is, if you request to be removed from our database), ChineseFoodDIY.com will keep your personal information in its archives.  Your information will then be used only as necessary for tax reasons or to prove  ChineseFoodDIY.com’s compliance with any applicable law. 

** 6.**

| 

** Accuracy of Personal Information**  
  
---|---  
  
ChineseFoodDIY.com will use reasonable efforts to keep customer personal information accurate for the Identified Purposes, and for minimizing the possibility of making inappropriate customer decisions based on such information.  Customers are responsible for informing ChineseFoodDIY.com about changes to their personal information.  You can do this by sending an email to  . ChineseFoodDIY.com will use new or updated personal information it receives from customers to update its own records. 

ChineseFoodDIY.com will use reasonable efforts to protect customers’ personal information.

** 8.**

| 

** Access to Personal Information**  
  
---|---  
  
ChineseFoodDIY.com will afford you a reasonable opportunity to review the personal information in your file, if you so request by  sending email to  .

If ChineseFoodDIY.com is not able to provide access to some aspect of a customer’s personal information, it will provide reasons for denying access such as; that by doing so would likely reveal personal information about a third party, or that it is confidential commercial information or attorney–client privileged communications, or that the information relates to a breach of an agreement or a contravention of law, or that its disclosure could reasonably be expected to threaten the life or security of another individual.

Customers have the right to request that inaccurate or incomplete information be amended as appropriate, by contacting ChineseFoodDIY.com or the Privacy Officer as described above.  ChineseFoodDIY.com will promptly correct such personal information. 

9\. Use of Cookies and Web Beacons

 We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. We also use third party advertising services to display advertisements, such as Google through the Google AdSense program. Some or all of those advertising services may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will send these advertisers information about your visit including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes. Geo-targeting is sometimes used for the purposes of matching advertisements with visitors based on certain attributes that visitor has. An example of this type of geo-targeting would be showing Idaho movie theatre ads to someone located in Idaho, or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited, such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites. DoubleClick DART cookies We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google.s DoubleClick service, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (.interest based targeting.). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Miami, you may see Miami hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses .non personally identifiable information.. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx You may choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added. 

10\. **Use of Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the type of browser you used to visit our site (such as Google Chrome, Internet Explorer or Mozilla Firefox), the time at which you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.
